[
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "தீப்புண்",
    "answers": ["தீப்புண்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "question": "துப்பாக்கி",
    "answers": ["துப்பாக்கி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "question": "சுரப்பி",
    "answers": ["சுரப்பி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "question": "சுயரூபம்",
    "answers": ["சுயரூபம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "question": "நாயகன்",
    "answers": ["நாயகன்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "question": "உன்னிப்பு",
    "answers": ["உன்னிப்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "question": "மாகாணம்",
    "answers": ["மாகாணம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "question": "புழக்கம்",
    "answers": ["புழக்கம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "question": "செய்தித்தாள்",
    "answers": ["செய்தித்தாள்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "question": "பாட்டி",
    "answers": ["பாட்டி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "question": "நோயாளி",
    "answers": ["நோயாளி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "question": "இருமல்",
    "answers": ["இருமல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "question": "கைத்தடி",
    "answers": ["கைத்தடி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "question": "குழந்தை",
    "answers": ["குழந்தை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "question": "மருந்து",
    "answers": ["மருந்து"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "question": "கொண்டை",
    "answers": ["கொண்டை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "question": "படம்",
    "answers": ["படம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "question": "தாதி",
    "answers": ["தாதி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 301,
    "question": "தடுப்பூசி",
    "answers": ["தடுப்பூசி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 302,
    "question": "தலைக்கவசம்",
    "answers": ["தலைக்கவசம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 303,
    "question": "ஆரோக்கியம்",
    "answers": ["ஆரோக்கியம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 304,
    "question": "எரிசக்தி",
    "answers": ["எரிசக்தி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 305,
    "question": "குத்துச்சண்டை",
    "answers": ["குத்துச்சண்டை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 306,
    "question": "நோய்க்கிருமி",
    "answers": ["நோய்க்கிருமி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 307,
    "question": "பக்கவாதம்",
    "answers": ["பக்கவாதம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 308,
    "question": "ஆய்வுக்கூடம்",
    "answers": ["ஆய்வுக்கூடம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
